https://asu.org/footer/privacy/

PrivacyYou are here: Home / Footer / PrivacyONLINE PRIVACY NOTICEEffective date: 9/1/2018Contents – Major HeadingsIntroductionWho we areHow to contact usHow we collect personal dataPersonal data we collect from othersCookies“Do not track” signalsHow we use your personal dataSelling of your personal dataChildren and privacySecurity and StorageYour rightsChanges to this Privacy NoticeIntroductionThis Privacy Notice explains how the Aikido Schools of Ueshiba (“ASU”, “we” or “us”) collects and processes your Personal Data. Each time you use our Site, the current version of the Privacy Notice will apply. Accordingly, whenever you use our Site, you should check the date of this Privacy Notice (which appears at the top) and review any changes since the last version. This Privacy Notice is applicable to all Site visitors, registered users, and all other users of our Site.“Personal Data” is any information that enables us to identify you, directly or indirectly, by reference to an identifier such as your name, identification number, location data, online identifier or one or more factors specific to your physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity.By visiting asu.org (the “Site”), you acknowledge that you have read and understood the processes and policies referred to in this Privacy Notice.Who we areFor the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (the “GDPR”), the Data Controller is ASU, registered in Montana and Florida, United States with a registered address at 6706 N Nebraska Ave #9746, Tampa, Florida 33674. Our nominated representative for the purposes of the GDPR Don Ellingsworth.How to contact usIf you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Notice, please contact us by sending an email to gdpr@nullasu.org or by post to ASU, 6706 N Nebraska Ave #9746, Tampa, Florida 33674.How we collect personal dataPersonal data we collect about you as a member of ASUIf you are a designated representative of an ASU school, with regard to each of your visits to the Site we may automatically collect the following information:Site access and usage informationContact information, description, social media links, location, instructors, and other information you may provide us regarding your school or institutionDate, location, cost, description and other information you may provide us regarding affiliated events that you are hostingYour location and time zoneRank and training informationMembership informationPersonal data we collect about you as a Site visitorWe do not collect Personal Data about Site visitors.Personal Data that you give us as a Site visitorThe Site maintains a voluntary opt-in email address list, in which you as a Site visitor may provide your email contact information in order to receive news and updates about ASU events and activities. The Site does not collect any other Personal Data for this purpose.Personal data we collect from othersThis is information we receive about you if you use any of the other websites (operated by us, or another member of our group) or use any other services provided by another member of our group or us.Non-Personal DataWe collect information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser and we may use this information to generate aggregate statistics about visitors to our Site, including, without limitation:Anonymized, partial (non-identifying)IP addressesBrowser type and plug-in detailsDevice type (e.g., desktop, laptop, tablet, phone, etc.)Operating systemLocal time zoneWe may use non-Personal Data for various business purposes such as providing customer service, market research, and improving our Site. Please check your web browser if you want to learn what information your browser sends or how to change your settings.CookiesLike many websites, our Site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of the Site. This helps us to analyze the use of the Site to customize and improve the content and the layout of the Site.When you first access the Site, you will receive a message advising you that cookies are in use. By continuing to browse the Site, you agree to our use of cookies as described in this Privacy Notice.You do not have to accept our cookies and can block them by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse all or some cookies. You may also delete them after they have been placed on your hard drive. If you do not accept or delete our cookies, some areas of the Site that you access may take more time to work, or may not function properly. For more information about cookies, visit: http://www.allaboutcookies.org.A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer, if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive.We use the following cookies:Strictly necessary cookies for registered members (instructors of ASU member schools) for logging on and accessing administrative features of the Site.Voluntary cookies for visitors who leave comments on Site articles, events, and posts.Google universal analytics, to help us count how many people visit the Site by tracking if you have visited before (expiration: 2 years).“Do not track” signalsWe do not respond to web browser “do not track” signals. As such, your navigation of our Site may be tracked as part of the gathering of quantitative user information described above. If you arrive at our Site by way of a link from a third party site that does respond to “do not track” requests, the recognition of any “do not track” request you have initiated will end as soon as you reach our Site.How we use your Personal DataWe will only process your Personal Data, including sharing it with third parties, where (1) you have provided your consent which can be withdrawn at any time, (2) the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or for administrative purposes regarding your membership in the ASU organization, (3) we are required by law, (4) processing is required to protect your vital interests or those of another person, or (5) processing is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate commercial interests, except where such interests are overridden by your rights and interests.We may use Personal Data for the following purposes:Personal Data you give to usWe will use this Personal Data:to carry out our obligations arising from your membership and/or the membership of your school’s students, and to provide you with the information and membership services;to organize and disseminate events, and to provide you with information, and other materials, relating to the content of the event, the instructors, and other attendees;to provide our newsletter and updates from the ASU Board and Administration;to respond to your questions and provide related membership services;to ensure that content from our Site is presented most effectively for you and your computer.Information we collect about youWe will use this Personal Data:to administer our Site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical purposes;to improve our Site to ensure that content is presented most effectively for you and your computer;as part of our efforts to keep our Site safe and secure.Personal Data we receive from other sourcesWe will combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We will use this information and the combined Personal Data for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).When we share and who can access your personal dataWe may share your Personal Data for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice with:Instructors of ASU affiliated schoolsAdministrators, Officers, and Board Members of the ASU organizationanalytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimization of our SiteWe will not sell your Personal Data to third parties for their use without your consent.Children and privacyOur Site is not directed to children under the age of 13, if you are not 13 years or older, do not use our Site. We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If we learn that Personal Data of persons less than 13 years-of-age has been collected through our Site, we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.Security and storageSecurityAlthough we use security measures to help protect your Personal Data against loss, misuse or unauthorized disclosure, we cannot guarantee the security of information transmitted to us over the internet.Transfer of personal data outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and international usersWe will not transfer Personal Data, relating to individuals within the European Economic Area (“EEA”), to third parties (i.e., those outside of our organization), located outside of the EEA without ensuring adequate protection under European law.Selling your personal dataWe are headquartered in the United States. Your Personal Data may be accessed by us or transferred to us in the United States or to our affiliates, partners, or service providers who are located worldwide. If you are visiting our Site from outside the United States, be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located, and our central database is operated. By using our Service, you consent to any transfer of this information.How long we store your personal dataWe will store your Personal Data, in a form which permits us to identify you, for no longer than is necessary for the purpose for which the Personal Data is processed. We may retain and use your Personal Data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements and rights, or if it is not technically reasonably feasible to remove it. Consistent with these requirements, we will try to delete your Personal Data quickly upon request. For member schools and individual members of the ASU, your Personal Data will be retained as long as you continue to be a member in good standing with the organization. We maintain one or more databases to store your Personal Data and may keep such information indefinitely.Where we store your personal dataAll information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure.The Personal Data that you provide to us is generally stored on servers located in the United States. If you are located in another jurisdiction, you should be aware that once your Personal Data is submitted through our Site, it will be transferred to our servers in the United States and that the United States currently does not have uniform data protection laws in place.Your rightsCorrection and removalIf any of the information that we have about you is incorrect, or you wish to have information (including Personal Data) removed from our records, please contact us at gdpr@nullasu.org.Opting OutMessages and communications for the purposes of marketing, administration, or membership support are sent only to designated administrative contacts of affiliated ASU schools.Our Site maintains a voluntary opt-in list in which individuals may submit their email address to receive communication regarding ASU-related events and news. Any individual who wishes to no longer receive communications generated from this list may let us know by clicking on the unsubscribe link within any marketing message that you receive, or by sending a message to us at guy@nullasu.org.Your European RightsYou have the right to ask us not to process your Personal Data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your Personal Data) if we intend to use your Personal Data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your Personal Data. You can also exercise the right by contacting us using the Contact Us section on our Site.Under European data protection law, in certain circumstances, you have the right to: Request access to your Personal DataRequest correction of your PersonalData Request erasure of your PersonalData Object to processing of your Personal DataRequest restriction of processing your Personal DataRequest transfer of your Personal DataWithdraw your consentIn addition, where you believe that ASU has not complied with its obligations under this Privacy Notice or European law, you have the right to make a complaint to an EU Data Protection Authority, such as the UK Information Commissioner’s Office.You can exercise any of these rights by contacting us by email at gdpr@nullasu.org].Your Californian RightsFOR RESIDENTS OF CALIFORNIA ONLY. Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code requires select businesses to disclose policies relating to the sharing of certain categories of your Personal Data with third parties. If you reside in California and have provided your Personal Data to Company, you may request information about our disclosures of certain categories of Personal data to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us at one of the following addresses: gdpr@nullasu.org orAikido Schools of Ueshiba6706 N Nebraska Ave #9746Tampa, Florida 33674Attn: California Privacy RightsChanges to this Privacy NoticeIf we make any material changes to this Privacy Notice or the way we use, share or collect personal Data, we will notify you by revising the “Effective Date” at the top of this Privacy Notice, prominently posting an announcement of the changes on our Site, or sending an email to the email address you most recently provided us (unless we do not have such an email address) prior to the new policy taking effect.Any changes we make to our Privacy Notice in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notification sent to you by e-mail if you are registered on our site. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to this Privacy Notice.Official ASU Board CommunicationsMemoriamSep 20, 2020 8:16 pmKeeping the dojo open while the building is closedMar 28, 2020 5:19 pmGeneral ASU NewsMemoriamSep 20, 2020 8:16 pmLiving by Design: A Biography of Mitsugi Saotome Shihan, Senior Student of O’Sensei and Founder of the Aikido Schools of UeshibaJul 13, 2020 6:10 pmCondolences: Thurston CarletonApr 14, 2020 2:54 pmUpcoming Events Ikeda Sensei Zoom Seminar December 12 @ 10:00 am - 4:00 pm ASU Winter Intensive 2021 – Online! January 1, 2021 @ 12:00 pm - January 3, 2021 @ 4:00 pm View All Events Social UpdatesComments Box SVG iconsUsed for the like, share, comment, and reaction iconsAikido Schools of Ueshiba
3 weeks agoKevin Choate's Syncopated Jo Kata by Marsha Turner 6th Dan ... See MoreSee LessView on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by EmailLikes: 28Shares: 7Comments: 0Comment on FacebookAikido Schools of Ueshiba
4 weeks agoNo-contact Basic Aikido Techniques #1 - Ikkyo, Nikkyo, Sankyo, Yonkyo With Jo - YouTube ... See MoreSee LessNo-contact Basic Aikido Techniques #1 - Ikkyo, Nikkyo, Sankyo, Yonkyo With Jo - YouTubeMany Aikido schools are planning for phased options during the progress of the COVID19 pandemic, and are looking for training options in between "solo practice"... View on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by EmailLikes: 28Shares: 5Comments: 1Comment on FacebookTokyo?Aikido Schools of Ueshiba
1 month agoPhotos from Aikido Schools of Ueshiba's post ... See MoreSee Less+1View on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by EmailLikes: 175Shares: 33Comments: 1Comment on FacebookLe envié un libro el arte de la longevidad en espaniol hace unos anios un presente de UruguayLoad more
Scroll to top
